（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
（空气爆裂声）
(air popping)
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
- 所以培训师 API。
- So Trainer API.
所以 Transformers Library 提供了一个 Trainer API
So Transformers Library provides a Trainer API
让你轻松找到调谐变压器模型
that allows you to easily find tune transformers models
在你的数据集上。
on your dataset.
所以 Trainer 类接受你的数据集，
So Trainer class takes your datasets,
你的模型以及训练超参数
your model as well as the training hyperparameters
并且可以在任何类型的设置上进行训练，
and can perform the training on any kind of setup,
CPU、GPU、多个 GPU、TPU
CPU, GPU, multiple GPUs, TPUs
也可以计算预测
can also compute the predictions
在任何数据集上，如果你提供了指标
on any dataset and if you provided metrics
在任何数据集上评估你的模型。
evaluate your model on any dataset.
你还可以涉及最终数据处理
You can also involve final data processing
比如动态填充，
such as dynamic padding,
只要你提供分词器
as long as you provide the tokenizer
或给定数据整理器。
or given data collator.
我们将在 MRPC 数据集上尝试这个 API，
We will try this API on the MRPC dataset,
因为它相对较小且易于预处理。
since it's relatively small and easy to preprocess.
正如我们在数据集概述视频中看到的那样，
As we saw in the Datasets overview video,
但是我们可以对其进行预处理。
however we can preprocess it.
我们在预处理期间不应用填充，
We do not apply padding during the preprocessing,
因为我们将使用动态填充
as we will use dynamic padding
在 DataCollatorWithPadding 之前。
before DataCollatorWithPadding.
请注意，我们不执行最后的步骤
Note that we don't do the final steps
重命名删除列
of renaming removing columns
或将格式设置为火炬张量。
or set the format to torch tensors.
所以 Trainer 会自动为我们做这一切
So Trainer will do all of this automatically for us
通过分析模型签名。
by analyzing the model signature.
创建培训师之前的最后一步是
The last step before creating the Trainer are
定义模型
to define a model
和一些训练超参数。
and some training hyperparameters.
我们在模型 API 视频中看到了第一个。
We saw to do the first in the model API video.
第二次我们使用 TrainingArguments 类。
For the second we use the TrainingArguments class.
它只需要一个文件夹的路径
It only takes a path to a folder
结果和检查点将保存在哪里，
where results and checkpoint will be saved,
但你也可以自定义所有超参数
but you can also customize all the hyperparameters
你的教练会使用，
your Trainer will use,
学习权重、训练影响数等。等等。
learning weight, number of training impacts, et. cetera.
创建培训师非常容易
It's been very easy to create a Trainer
并开展培训。
and launch a training.
你应该显示一个进度条
You should display a progress bar
如果你在 GPU 上运行，几分钟后
and after a few minutes if you're running on a GPU
你应该完成培训。
you should have the training finished.
然而，结果将是相当虎头蛇尾，
The result will be rather anticlimactic however,
因为你只会得到训练损失
as you will only get a training loss
这并没有真正告诉你任何事情
which doesn't really tell you anything
关于你的模型表现如何。
about how well your model is performing.
这是因为我们没有指定任何指标
This is because we didn't specify any metric
用于评估。
for the evaluation.
要获得这些指标，
To get those metrics,
我们将首先收集预测
we will first gather the predictions
使用预测方法在整个评估集上。
on the whole evaluation set using the predict method.
它返回一个包含三个字段的命名元组，
It returns a namedtuple with three fields,
预测，其中包含预测模型。
Prediction, which contains the model of predictions.
Label_IDs，其中包含标签
Label_IDs, which contains the labels
如果你的数据集有它们
if your dataset had them
和此处为空的指标。
and metrics which is empty here.
我们正在努力做到这一点。
We're trying to do that.
预测是模型的对数
The predictions are the logits of the models
对于数据集中的所有句子。
for all the sentences in the dataset.
所以一个形状为 408 x 2 的 NumPy 数组。
So a NumPy array of shape 408 by 2.
为了将它们与我们的标签相匹配，
To match them with our labels,
我们需要采取最大的 logit
we need to take the maximum logit
对于每个预测
for each prediction
知道预测了这两个类别中的哪一个。
to know which of the two classes was predicted.
我们使用 argmax 函数来做到这一点。
We do this with the argmax function.
然后我们可以使用数据集库中的指标。
Then we can use a metric from the Datasets library.
它可以像数据集一样轻松加载
It can be loaded as easily as a dataset
具有负载度量功能
with the load metric function
并且每个返回用于数据集的评估指标。
and each returns the evaluation metric used for the dataset.
我们可以看到我们的模型确实学到了一些东西
We can see our model did learn something
因为它的准确率为 85.7%。
as it is 85.7% accurate.
在训练期间监控评估矩阵，
To monitor the evaluation matrix during training,
我们需要定义一个 compute_metrics 函数
we need to define a compute_metrics function
和以前一样的步骤。
that does the same step as before.
它需要一个带有预测和标签的命名元组
It takes a namedtuple with predictions and labels
并且必须返回一个字典
and must return a dictionary
使用我们想要跟踪的指标。
with the metrics we want to keep track of.
通过 epoch 评估策略
By passing the epoch evaluation strategy
对于我们的训练论点，
to our training arguments,
我们告诉培训师评估
we tell the Trainer to evaluate
在每个纪元的末尾。
at the end of every epoch.
在笔记本中启动培训
Launching a training inside a notebook
然后会显示一个进度条
will then display a progress bar
并在你通过每个纪元时完成你在这里看到的表格。
and complete the table you see here as you pass every epoch.
（空气呼啸）
(air whooshing)
（空气渐弱）
(air decrescendos)